[
  {
    "question": "How are Workflows moved between instances?",
    "options": [
      "Workflows are moved using Update Sets",
      "Workflows are moved using Transform Maps",
      "Workflows are moved using Application Sets",
      "Workflows cannot be moved between instances"
    ],
    "correctAnswers": ["Workflows are moved using Update Sets"],
    "explanation": ""
  },
  {
    "question": "Which statement is true about business rules?",
    "options": [
      "A business rule must run before a database action occurs",
      "A business rule can be a piece of Javascript",
      "A business rule must not run before a database action occurs",
      "A business rule monitors fields on a form"
    ],
    "correctAnswers": ["A business rule can be a piece of Javascript"],
    "explanation": ""
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following allows a user to edit field values in a list without opening the form?",
    "options": [
      "Data Editor",
      "Edit Menu",
      "List Editor",
      "Form Designer"
    ],
    "correctAnswers": ["List Editor"],
    "explanation": ""
  },
  {
    "question": "What is a formatter?",
    "options": [
      "A formatter allows you to configure applications on your instance",
      "A formatter is a form element used to display information that is not a field in the record",
      "A formatter allows you to populate fields automatically",
      "A formatter is a set of conditions applied to a table to help find and work with data"
    ],
    "correctAnswers": ["A formatter is a form element used to display information that is not a field in the record"],
    "explanation": ""
  },
  {
    "question": "Which one of the following statements applies to a set of fields when they are coalesced during an import?",
    "options": [
      "If a match is found using the coalesce fields, the existing record is updated with the information being imported",
      "If a match is not found using the coalesce fields, the system does not create a Transform Map",
      "If a match is found using the coalesce fields, the system creates a new record",
      "If a match is not found using the coalesce fields, the existing record is updated"
    ],
    "correctAnswers": ["If a match is found using the coalesce fields, the existing record is updated with the information being imported"],
    "explanation": ""
  },
  {
    "question": "Which ServiceNow products can be used to discover and populate the CMDB?",
    "options": [
      "Discovery",
      "IntegrationHub ETL",
      "Finder",
      "CMDB Plug-in",
      "CMDB Integration Dashboard"
    ],
    "correctAnswers": ["Discovery", "IntegrationHub ETL"],
    "explanation": ""
  },
  {
    "question": "Which are valid ServiceNow User Authentication Methods?",
    "options": [
      "XML feed",
      "Local database",
      "LDAP",
      "SSO",
      "FTP authentication"
    ],
    "correctAnswers": ["Local database", "LDAP", "SSO"],
    "explanation": ""
  },
  {
    "question": "Which concepts are associated with the ServiceNow CMDB?",
    "options": [
      "Service Processes",
      "User Permissions",
      "Tables and Fields",
      "A Database",
      "The Dependency View"
    ],
    "correctAnswers": ["Service Processes", "Tables and Fields", "A Database", "The Dependency View"],
    "explanation": ""
  },
  {
    "question": "Which tool is used to have conversations with logged-in users in real-time?",
    "options": ["Connect Chat", "Now Messenger", "User Presence", "Comments"],
    "correctAnswers": ["Connect Chat"],
    "explanation": ""
  },
  {
    "question": "What is generated from the Service Catalog once a user places an order?",
    "options": ["A change request", "An Order Guide", "A request", "An SLA"],
    "correctAnswers": ["A request"],
    "explanation": ""
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the purpose of a Related List?",
    "options": [
      "To create a one-to-many relationship",
      "To dot-walk to a core table",
      "To present related fields",
      "To present related records"
    ],
    "correctAnswers": ["To present related records"],
    "explanation": ""
  },
  {
    "question": "What is a Record Producer?",
    "options": [
      "A type of Catalog Item used for Requests, not Services",
      "Creates user records",
      "A type of Catalog Item that provides easy ordering by bundling requests",
      "A type of Catalog Item that allows users to create task-based records from the Service Catalog"
    ],
    "correctAnswers": ["A type of Catalog Item that allows users to create task-based records from the Service Catalog"],
    "explanation": ""
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the Import Set Table?",
    "options": [
      "A table where data will be placed, post-transformation",
      "A table that determines relationships",
      "A staging area for imported records",
      "A repository for Update Set information"
    ],
    "correctAnswers": ["A staging area for imported records"],
    "explanation": ""
  },
  {
    "question": "What is a Dictionary Override?",
    "options": [
      "Incoming customer update in an Update Set for same objects",
      "Addition, modification, or removal affecting IT services",
      "A task in a flow requesting an action",
      "Sets field properties in extended tables"
    ],
    "correctAnswers": ["Sets field properties in extended tables"],
    "explanation": ""
  },
  {
    "question": "Which term refers to application menus and modules you may want to access quickly?",
    "options": ["Breadcrumb", "Favorite", "Tag", "Bookmark"],
    "correctAnswers": ["Favorite"],
    "explanation": ""
  },
  {
    "question": "Which group of permissions is used to control Application and Module access?",
    "options": ["Access Control Rules", "UI Policies", "Roles", "Assignment Rules"],
    "correctAnswers": ["Roles"],
    "explanation": ""
  },
  {
    "question": "Which three Variable Types can be added to a Service Catalog Item?",
    "options": [
      "True/False, Multiple Choice, and Ordered",
      "True/False, Checkbox, and Number List",
      "Number List, Single Line Text, and Reference",
      "Multiple Choice, Select Box, and Checkbox"
    ],
    "correctAnswers": ["Multiple Choice, Select Box, and Checkbox"],
    "explanation": ""
  },
  {
    "question": "A Service Catalog may include which of the following components?",
    "options": [
      "Order Guides, Exchange Rates, Calendars",
      "Order Guides, Catalog Items, and Interceptors",
      "Catalog Items, Asset Contracts, Task Surveys",
      "Record Producers, Order Guides, and Catalog Items"
    ],
    "correctAnswers": ["Record Producers", "Order Guides", "Catalog Items"],
    "explanation": ""
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the name of the conversational bot platform that provides assistance?",
    "options": ["Answer Agent", "Live Feed", "Virtual Agent", "Connect Chat"],
    "correctAnswers": ["Virtual Agent"],
    "explanation": ""
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following can be customized through the Basic Configuration UI 16 module?",
    "options": ["Banner Image", "Record Number Format", "Browser Tab Title", "System Date Format", "Form Header Size"],
    "correctAnswers": ["Banner Image", "Browser Tab Title", "Form Header Size"],
    "explanation": ""
  },
  {
    "question": "What information does the System Dictionary contain?",
    "options": [
      "The human-readable labels and language settings",
      "The definition for each table and column",
      "The information on how tables relate to each other",
      "The language dictionary used for spell checking"
    ],
    "correctAnswers": ["The definition for each table and column"],
    "explanation": ""
  },
  {
    "question": "Buttons, form links, and context menu items are all examples of what type of functionality?",
    "options": ["Business Rule", "UI Action", "Client Script", "UI Policy"],
    "correctAnswers": ["UI Action"],
    "explanation": ""
  },
  {
    "question": "A REQ number in the Service Catalog represents:",
    "options": ["the order number", "the stage", "the task to complete", "the individual item in the order"],
    "correctAnswers": ["the order number"],
    "explanation": ""
  },
  {
    "question": "Which one of the following statements best describes the purpose of an Update Set?",
    "options": [
      "An Update Set allows administrators to group a series of changes into a named set and then move this set as a unit to other systems",
      "By default, an Update Set includes customizations, Business Rules, and homepages",
      "An Update Set is a group of customizations that is moved from Production to Development",
      "By default, the changes included in an Update Set are visible only in the instance to which they are applied"
    ],
    "correctAnswers": ["An Update Set allows administrators to group a series of changes into a named set and then move this set as a unit to other systems"],
    "explanation": ""
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the platform name for the User table?",
    "options": ["u_users", "sys_users", "x_users", "sys_user"],
    "correctAnswers": ["sys_user"],
    "explanation": ""
  },
  {
    "question": "In what order should filter elements be specified?",
    "options": [
      "Field, Operator, then Value",
      "Field, Operator, then Condition",
      "Operator, Condition, then Value",
      "Value, Operator, then Field"
    ],
    "correctAnswers": ["Field, Operator, then Value"],
    "explanation": ""
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following is used to initiate a flow?",
    "options": ["A Trigger", "Core Action", "A spoke", "An Event"],
    "correctAnswers": ["An Event"],
    "explanation": ""
  },
  {
    "question": "Which one of the following statements is true about Column Context Menus?",
    "options": [
      "It displays actions such as creating quick reports, configuring the list, and exporting data",
      "It displays actions related to filtering options, assigning tags, and search",
      "It displays actions related to viewing and filtering the entire list",
      "It displays actions such as view form, view related task, and add relationship"
    ],
    "correctAnswers": ["It displays actions such as creating quick reports, configuring the list, and exporting data"],
    "explanation": ""
  },
  {
    "question": "Which one of the following statements is a recommendation from ServiceNow about Update Sets?",
    "options": [
      "Avoid using the Default Update set as an Update Set for moving customizations from instance to instance",
      "Before moving customizations from instance to instance with Update Sets, ensure that both instances are different versions",
      "Use the Baseline Update Set to store the contents of items after they are changed the first time",
      "Once an Update Set is closed as In Progress change it back to Complete until it is applied to another instance"
    ],
    "correctAnswers": ["Avoid using the Default Update set as an Update Set for moving customizations from instance to instance"],
    "explanation": ""
  },
  {
    "question": "What is a characteristic about Service Catalog variables?",
    "options": [
      "Service Catalog variables can only be used in Record Producers",
      "Service Catalog variables can only be used in Order Guides",
      "Service Catalog variables cannot affect the order price",
      "Service Catalog variables are global by default"
    ],
    "correctAnswers": ["Service Catalog variables are global by default"],
    "explanation": ""
  },
  {
    "question": "Access Control rules may be defined with which of the following permission requirements?",
    "options": ["Roles", "Conditional Expressions", "Assignment Rules", "Scripts", "User Criteria", "Groups"],
    "correctAnswers": ["Roles", "User Criteria", "Groups"],
    "explanation": ""
  },
  {
    "question": "When searching using the App Navigator, what can be returned?",
    "options": [
      "Names of Applications and Modules",
      "Names of Modules",
      "Names of Applications",
      "Favorites",
      "History Records",
      "Titles of Dashboard Gauges"
    ],
    "correctAnswers": ["Names of Applications and Modules", "Favorites", "History Records", "Titles of Dashboard Gauges"],
    "explanation": ""
  },
  {
    "question": "What is a schema map?",
    "options": [
      "Enables defining records as trouble sources for CIs",
      "Graphically organizes visual task boards for the CMDB",
      "Graphically displays the CIs that support a business service",
      "Displays details of tables and their relationships visually"
    ],
    "correctAnswers": ["Displays details of tables and their relationships visually"],
    "explanation": ""
  },
  {
    "question": "The display sequence is controlled in a Service Catalog Item using which field?",
    "options": [
      "The Default Value field in the Catalog Item form",
      "The Sequence field in the Catalog Item form",
      "The Order field in the Variable form",
      "The Choice field in the Variable form"
    ],
    "correctAnswers": ["The Order field in the Variable form"],
    "explanation": ""
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the difference between Insert and Update operations on a form?",
    "options": [
      "Insert creates a new record and Update saves changes, both remain on the form",
      "Insert creates a new record and Update saves changes, both exit the form",
      "Insert saves changes and exits the form, Update saves changes and remains on the form",
      "Insert saves changes and remains on the form, Update saves changes and exits the form"
    ],
    "correctAnswers": ["Insert saves changes and exits the form, Update saves changes and remains on the form"],
    "explanation": ""
  },
  {
    "question": "Which statement is true when a new table is created by extending another table?",
    "options": [
      "The new table archives the parent table and assumed its roles in the database",
      "The new table inherits all of the Business Rules, Client Scripts, and UI Policies of the parent table, but none of the existing fields",
      "The new table inherits all of the fields of the parent table and can also contain new fields unique to itself",
      "The new table inherits all of the fields, but does not inherit Access Control rules, Client Scripts, and UI Policies of the parent table"
    ],
    "correctAnswers": ["The new table inherits all of the fields of the parent table and can also contain new fields unique to itself"],
    "explanation": ""
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the function of user impersonation?",
    "options": [
      "Testing and visibility",
      "Activate verbose logging",
      "View custom perspectives",
      "Unlock Application master list"
    ],
    "correctAnswers": ["Testing and visibility"],
    "explanation": ""
  },
  {
    "question": "As it relates to ServiceNow reporting, what is a metric?",
    "options": [
      "A metric is a report gauge used on homepages to display real-time data",
      "A metric is a time measurement used to report the effectiveness of workflows and SLAs",
      "A metric is used to measure and evaluate the effectiveness of IT service management processes",
      "A metric is a comparative measurement used to report the effectiveness of flows and SLAs"
    ],
    "correctAnswers": ["A metric is used to measure and evaluate the effectiveness of IT service management processes"],
    "explanation": ""
  },
  {
    "question": "Which statement describes the purpose of an Order Guide?",
    "options": [
      "Order Guides restrict the number of items in an order to only one item per request",
      "Order Guide provide a list of guidelines for Administrators on how to set up item variables",
      "Order Guide provide the ability to order multiple, related items as one request",
      "Order Guides take the user directly to the checkout without prompting for information"
    ],
    "correctAnswers": ["Order Guide provide the ability to order multiple, related items as one request"],
    "explanation": ""
  },
  {
    "question": "Which types of client scripts are supported in ServiceNow?",
    "options": [
      "onSubmit",
      "onUpdate",
      "onCellEdit",
      "onLoad",
      "onChange",
      "onSave"
    ],
    "correctAnswers": ["onSubmit", "onCellEdit", "onLoad", "onChange"],
    "explanation": ""
  },
  {
    "question": "Table Access Control rules are processed in which order?",
    "options": [
      "any table name (wildcard), parent table name, table name",
      "table name, parent table name, any table name (wildcard)",
      "parent table name, table name, any table name (wildcard)",
      "any table name (wildcard), table name, parent table name"
    ],
    "correctAnswers": ["table name, parent table name, any table name (wildcard)"],
    "explanation": ""
  },
  {
    "question": "Which technique is used to get information from a series of referenced fields from different tables?",
    "options": [
      "Table-Walking",
      "Sys_ID Pulling",
      "Dot-Walking",
      "Record-Hopping"
    ],
    "correctAnswers": ["Dot-Walking"],
    "explanation": ""
  },
  {
    "question": "Which one of the following statements describes the contents of the Configuration Management Database (CMDB)?",
    "options": [
      "The CMDB contains data about tangible and intangible business assets",
      "The CMDB contains the Business Rules that direct the intangible, configurable assets used by a company",
      "The CMDB archives all Service Management PaaS equipment metadata and usage statistics",
      "The CMDB contains ITIL process data pertaining to configuration items"
    ],
    "correctAnswers": ["The CMDB contains data about tangible and intangible business assets"],
    "explanation": ""
  },
  {
    "question": "Where can Admins check which release is running on a ServiceNow instance?",
    "options": [
      "Memory Stats module",
      "Stats module",
      "System.upgraded table",
      "Transactions log"
    ],
    "correctAnswers": ["Stats module"],
    "explanation": ""
  },
  {
    "question": "When using the Load Data and Transform Map process, what is the Mapping Assist used for?",
    "options": [
      "Mapping fields using the Import Log",
      "Mapping fields using Transform History",
      "Mapping fields using an SLA",
      "Mapping fields using a Field Map"
    ],
    "correctAnswers": ["Mapping fields using a Field Map"],
    "explanation": ""
  },
  {
    "question": "How is the Event Log different from the Event Registry?",
    "options": [
      "Event Log contains generated Events, the Event Registry is a table of Event definitions",
      "Event Log is formatted in the Log style, the Event Registry displays different fields",
      "Event Log lists Events that were triggered by integrations, the Event Registry lists the Events triggered during the day",
      "Event Log is the same as the Event Registry"
    ],
    "correctAnswers": ["Event Log contains generated Events, the Event Registry is a table of Event definitions"],
    "explanation": ""
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the path an Administrator could take to view the fulfillment stage task list for an order placed by a user?",
    "options": [
      "RITM (Number)>REQ (Number)>PROCUREMENT (Number)",
      "REQ (Number)>RITM (Number)>PROCUREMENT (Number)",
      "REQ (Number)>RITM (Number)>TASK (Number)",
      "FULFILLMENT (Number)>RITM (Number)>TASK (Number)"
    ],
    "correctAnswers": ["REQ (Number)>RITM (Number)>TASK (Number)"],
    "explanation": ""
  },
  {
    "question": "Which would NOT appear in the History section of the Application Navigator?",
    "options": ["Records", "UI Pages", "Lists", "Forms"],
    "correctAnswers": ["UI Pages"],
    "explanation": ""
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following is true of Service Catalog Items in relation to the Service Catalog?",
    "options": ["They run behind the scenes.", "They are the building blocks.", "They are optional.", "They provide options."],
    "correctAnswers": ["They are the building blocks."],
    "explanation": ""
  },
  {
    "question": "From the User menu, which actions can a user select?",
    "options": ["Send Notifications", "Log Out ServiceNow", "Elevate Roles", "Impersonate Users", "Order from Service Catalog", "Approve Records"],
    "correctAnswers": ["Elevate Roles", "Impersonate Users", "Approve Records"],
    "explanation": ""
  },
  {
    "question": "What module in the Service Catalog application does an Administrator access to begin creating a new item?",
    "options": ["Maintain Categories", "Maintain Items", "Content Items", "Items"],
    "correctAnswers": ["Maintain Items"],
    "explanation": ""
  },
  {
    "question": "A knowledge article must be which of the following states to display to a user?",
    "options": ["Published", "Drafted", "Retired", "Reviewed"],
    "correctAnswers": ["Published"],
    "explanation": ""
  },
  {
    "question": "Which term best describes something that is created, has work performed upon it, and is eventually moved to a state of closed?",
    "options": ["report", "flow", "event", "task"],
    "correctAnswers": ["task"],
    "explanation": ""
  },
  {
    "question": "Knowledge Base Search results can be sorted by which of the following?",
    "options": ["Most recent update", "Popularity", "Relevancy", "Manager assignment", "Number of views"],
    "correctAnswers": ["Most recent update", "Relevancy", "Number of views"],
    "explanation": ""
  },
  {
    "question": "What allows agents to initiate a group discussion from a Workspace task-based or interaction-based record?",
    "options": ["Connect Hub", "Sidebar", "Help Menu", "Chatbot", "Virtual Agent"],
    "correctAnswers": ["Sidebar"],
    "explanation": ""
  },
  {
    "question": "What tool allows you to drag and drop to specify links between source fields on an import set table and destination fields on any ServiceNow table?",
    "options": ["import workspace", "data source map", "Mapping assist utility", "import designer", "transform designer", "transform dashboard"],
    "correctAnswers": ["Mapping assist utility"],
    "explanation": ""
  },
  {
    "question": "By default, a report is shared with the following:",
    "options": ["All roles", "The report creator only", "Only groups that the report creator belongs to", "All users and groups"],
    "correctAnswers": ["The report creator only"],
    "explanation": ""
  },
  {
    "question": "On a business rule, which setting determines at what points the rule executes? What are the options for specifying that timing?",
    "options": ["Prior to, synchronous, on update", "Insert, update, delete, query", "Before, synchronous, schedule job, views", "Before, after, Async, display"],
    "correctAnswers": ["Before, after, Async, display"],
    "explanation": ""
  },
  {
    "question": "What is created by default when you create a new table? (Select 2 Answers)",
    "options": ["A table-specific admin role", "Application Menu with the same name as the table label", "Module with the plural of the table label", "Dashboard to manage the table's activity"],
    "correctAnswers": ["Application Menu with the same name as the table label", "Module with the plural of the table label"],
    "explanation": ""
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following are the UI Actions in a form? (Select 3 Answers)",
    "options": ["Form context menu items (right-click the header)", "Form buttons", "Form access", "Form relationships", "Form links (related links in a form)"],
    "correctAnswers": ["Form context menu items (right-click the header)", "Form buttons", "Form links (related links in a form)"],
    "explanation": ""
  },
  {
    "question": "What are examples of UI actions relating to lists? (Choose 4 Answers)",
    "options": ["List buttons", "list context menu", "list choices", "list links", "list control", "lists overwrite"],
    "correctAnswers": ["List buttons", "list context menu", "list choices", "list links"],
    "explanation": ""
  },
  {
    "question": "What are the different Schema relationship types that are supported for tables? (Select 4 Answers)",
    "options": ["Referencing", "Referenced By", "Depended By", "Depending", "Exteded by", "Extending"],
    "correctAnswers": ["Referencing", "Referenced By", "Depended By", "Extending"],
    "explanation": ""
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following is a true statement regarding Flow Designer actions? (Select 3 Answers)",
    "options": ["Define when the flow is performed", "Can be contained in a spoke", "Require script to develop", "Represent reusable operations for use across multiple flows", "Provide the ability to build your custom actions"],
    "correctAnswers": ["Can be contained in a spoke", "Represent reusable operations for use across multiple flows", "Provide the ability to build your custom actions"],
    "explanation": ""
  },
  {
    "question": "What is a Configuration Item (CI)?",
    "options": ["Components of an infrastructure required to deliver a product or service", "A database used to store configuration records throughout their lifecycle", "Information that further describes a CI such as name, serial number, or operating system", "A set of tools and databases that are used to manage an organization's configuration data"],
    "correctAnswers": ["Components of an infrastructure required to deliver a product or service"],
    "explanation": ""
  },
  {
    "question": "What are the three types of Flow Designer triggers? (Select 3 Answers)",
    "options": ["Schedule-based", "work-based", "Record-based", "Role-Based", "Application-based"],
    "correctAnswers": ["Schedule-based", "Record-based", "Role-Based"],
    "explanation": ""
  },
  {
    "question": "Which CMDB feature tracks the activities and history of data sources as they insert and update CI attributes? (Select 2 Answers)",
    "options": ["CMDB 360", "CI Class Manager", "MultiSource CMDB", "CMDB Data Manager", "CMDB CI Lifecycle Management"],
    "correctAnswers": ["CMDB 360", "MultiSource CMDB"],
    "explanation": ""
  },
  {
    "question": "If a knowledge base has no access details specified, what users are able to read articles in that knowledge base?",
    "options": ["No users", "Itil users", "Users with kb_user role", "Any user with an articles permalink", "Any active user"],
    "correctAnswers": ["Any active user"],
    "explanation": ""
  },
  {
    "question": "What access control rules are created by default when creating a custom table? (Select 4 Answers)",
    "options": ["Create", "Write", "Archive", "Access", "Delete", "Read"],
    "correctAnswers": ["Create", "Write", "Delete", "Read"],
    "explanation": ""
  },
  {
    "question": "Who can add or remove widgets in a dashboard? (Select 3 Answers)",
    "options": ["Users with edit access to the dashboard", "User with dashboard_Admin role", "Dashboard owner", "User with report_admin role", "Users with view access to the dashboard"],
    "correctAnswers": ["Users with edit access to the dashboard", "User with dashboard_Admin role", "Dashboard owner"],
    "explanation": ""
  },
  {
    "question": "Which group of permissions is used to control Application and Module access?",
    "options": ["Access Control Rules", "UI Policies", "Roles", "Assignment Rules"],
    "correctAnswers": ["Roles"],
    "explanation": ""
  },
  {
    "question": "Which tool graphically displays an infrastructure view for a configuration item and its relationship with other CIs?",
    "options": ["Schema map", "Dependency view", "Dependency map", "Database view"],
    "correctAnswers": ["Dependency view"],
    "explanation": ""
  },
  {
    "question": "When a Flow runs an action, it generates a runtime value that stays the same for the duration of the flow. What is the name of that runtime value?",
    "options": ["Data pill runtime value", "Sequence runtime value", "Starting runtime value", "Trigger runtime value", "Input runtime value"],
    "correctAnswers": ["Data pill runtime value"],
    "explanation": ""
  },
  {
    "question": "Which field should you look at if you want a unique identifier record of 32 characters?",
    "options": ["sys_id", "unique_id", "primary-key", "char_id"],
    "correctAnswers": ["sys_id"],
    "explanation": ""
  },
  {
    "question": "When testing a catalog item having a manager approval flow, which best practices would you follow? (Choose 3 Answers)",
    "options": ["Make sure the latest flows are activated.", "Use the instance incognito setting to quickly toggle between requester and approver", "Impersonate the requester to ensure the form works", "Make sure the requester's user record has a manager specified.", "Create and select your testing Update set, before starting the test cases.", "Use your admin account, so you can approve the items quickly"],
    "correctAnswers": ["Make sure the latest flows are activated.", "Make sure the requester's user record has a manager specified.", "Create and select your testing Update set, before starting the test cases."],
    "explanation": ""
  },
  {
    "question": "A Product Owner cannot see tasks on ‘Service Desk > My Group Work List’. What could be the root cause?",
    "options": [
      "Product Owner is not a member of Development group",
      "Product Owner has no assignment group",
      "Product owner is accessing ServiceNow using incorrect credentials",
      "Product Owner does not have itil role"
    ],
    "correctAnswers": ["Product Owner does not have itil role"],
    "explanation": ""
  },
  {
    "question": "Which tab contains the Activity Stream for a task?",
    "options": ["Related Links", "Related Records", "Notes", "History", "Resolution Information"],
    "correctAnswers": ["Notes"],
    "explanation": ""
  },
  {
    "question": "Which ServiceNow resource can be used as a blueprint to map your IT services to ServiceNow?",
    "options": [
      "Configuration management database (CMDB)",
      "Now learning",
      "Servicenow wiki",
      "Service mapping guided setup",
      "Common service data model (CSDM)",
      "ITSM"
    ],
    "correctAnswers": ["Common service data model (CSDM)"],
    "explanation": ""
  },
  {
    "question": "As a System Admin, how can you protect an application by identifying and restricting access to application files and data?",
    "options": ["Access Control Rules", "Web Application Firewall", "Application Scope", "Integrated IAM With ServiceNow"],
    "correctAnswers": ["Application Scope"],
    "explanation": ""
  },
  {
    "question": "What are the steps for applying an update set to an instance? (Select 3 Answers)",
    "options": ["Preview", "Retrieve", "Copy", "Delete", "Commit"],
    "correctAnswers": ["Retrieve"],
    "explanation": ""
  },
  {
    "question": "Which tab on the Knowledge Base record would you use to identify the set of users who can read articles?",
    "options": ["Can read", "Access list", "Accessible to", "Can access"],
    "correctAnswers": ["Can read"],
    "explanation": ""
  },
  {
    "question": "The CMDB is the authoritative source of what information? (Select 3 Answers)",
    "options": ["Owner", "Support Group", "Server Log files", "Contents of all server and application configuration files", "Contact"],
    "correctAnswers": ["Owner", "Support Group", "Contact"],
    "explanation": ""
  },
  {
    "question": "An Incident Manager cannot see tasks in the ‘Service Desk > My Group Work’ list. What could explain this? (Select 2 Answers)",
    "options": [
      "The incident manager does not have the ITIL or service_fulfiller role",
      "The incident manager is not listed as the assignment group manager",
      "The incident manager is not part of the service desk group",
      "No incident task is assigned to any of the group members",
      "The incident manager is not a member of the critical incidents group"
    ],
    "correctAnswers": ["The incident manager does not have the ITIL or service_fulfiller role", "The incident manager is not a member of the critical incidents group"],
    "explanation": ""
  },
  {
    "question": "You can use the Data Management plugins to define table relationships or minimize performance issues. What are these plugins? (Select 3 Answers)",
    "options": ["Table cleaner", "Many to many task relations", "Data archiving", "Database rotations", "Schema map"],
    "correctAnswers": ["Many to many task relations", "Data archiving", "Database rotations"],
    "explanation": ""
  },
  {
    "question": "When implementing ITSM, where would you navigate to update the Now Platform UI branding including company logo and colors? (Select 2 Answers)",
    "options": [
      "System Properties > My Company",
      "Team Development > Properties",
      "Guided Setup > ITSM Guided Setup",
      "System Properties > Basic Configuration UI16"
    ],
    "correctAnswers": ["Guided Setup > ITSM Guided Setup", "System Properties > Basic Configuration UI16"],
    "explanation": ""
  },
  {
    "question": "When importing data, what happens to imported rows if no coalesce field is specified?",
    "options": [
      "All rows are treated as new records, but error will be flagged in the import log",
      "Duplicate rows are rejected from the import",
      "All rows are treated as new records. No existing records were updated",
      "All rows are rejected from the import, as coalesce field is required"
    ],
    "correctAnswers": ["All rows are treated as new records. No existing records were updated"],
    "explanation": ""
  },
  {
    "question": "Access controls are evaluated in this order. Within step one, what order are the table ACLs evaluated?",
    "options": [
      "General to specific: table ACL, table.Field ACL, parent table.Field ACL",
      "Specific to general: table.Field ACL, parent table.Field ACL, * Field ACL",
      "Top to bottom: wildcard table ACL, parent table ACL, table ACL",
      "Specific to general: table ACL, parent table ACL, wildcard(*)ACL"
    ],
    "correctAnswers": ["Specific to general: table ACL, parent table ACL, wildcard(*)ACL"],
    "explanation": ""
  },
  {
    "question": "What Visual Task Board type automatically updates the tasks when the respective cards are edited or change lanes?",
    "options": ["Flexible", "Guided", "Freeform", "List"],
    "correctAnswers": ["Guided"],
    "explanation": ""
  },
  {
    "question": "What are the different types of Client Scripts supported in ServiceNow? (Select 4 Answers)",
    "options": ["OnSave()", "OnChange()", "OnLoad()", "OnCellEdit()", "OnSubmit()", "OnDelete()"],
    "correctAnswers": ["OnChange()", "OnLoad()", "OnCellEdit()", "OnSubmit()"],
    "explanation": ""
  },
  {
    "question": "Define Import Set Table",
    "options": [
      "A record that defines where to get the data to import",
      "The conversion of data from an import set table to another table",
      "Staging location for records imported",
      "Update existing target table records when transforming import data"
    ],
    "correctAnswers": ["Staging location for records imported"],
    "explanation": ""
  },
  {
    "question": "What allows you to see more information on the same screen while using Visual Task Boards (VTB)?",
    "options": ["Card Thumbnails", "Compact Cards", "Minimize Tasks", "Card Groups"],
    "correctAnswers": ["Compact Cards"],
    "explanation": ""
  },
  {
    "question": "What CMDB Workspace feature lets you visualize the hierarchical map of CIs and relationships centered on a CI you choose?",
    "options": ["Service Mapping", "Visualization Designer", "Schema Map", "360º Relationship Visualization", "Unified Map"],
    "correctAnswers": ["Unified Map"],
    "explanation": ""
  },
  {
    "question": "Which section in the Report Designer is used to specify grouping and calculations to run against data?",
    "options": ["Data", "Format", "Configure", "Style", "Group by"],
    "correctAnswers": ["Configure"],
    "explanation": ""
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following are captured in an Update Set?",
    "options": ["Report Definitions", "Published Flows", "Business Rules", "New data Records", "Modified CIs"],
    "correctAnswers": ["Report Definitions", "Published Flows", "Business Rules"],
    "explanation": ""
  },
  {
    "question": "Where do you navigate to see the notifications currently defined on the Now Platform?",
    "options": [
      "System Definitions > Notifications",
      "System Definitions > Definitions",
      "System Definitions > Email > Notifications",
      "NotificationsSystem > Email > Definitions"
    ],
    "correctAnswers": ["System Definitions > Email > Notifications"],
    "explanation": ""
  },
  {
    "question": "What policy type should you use to enforce mandatory fields and read-only rules?",
    "options": ["UI Policy", "Connect Chat", "Data Policy", "Virtual Agent"],
    "correctAnswers": ["Data Policy"],
    "explanation": ""
  },
   {
    "question": "Which of the following statement is correct about Business Rules?",
    "options": [
      "Business rule could be Python script",
      "Business rule should run after a database action",
      "Business rule depends on form actions",
      "Business rule could be Javascript"
    ],
    "correctAnswers": ["Business rule could be Javascript"],
    "explanation": ""
  },
  {
    "question": "The display sequence is controlled in a Service Catalog Item using which of the following?",
    "options": [
      "The Default value field in the Catalog item form",
      "The Sequence field in the Catalog Item form",
      "The Order field in the Variable form",
      "The Choice field in the variable form"
    ],
    "correctAnswers": ["The Order field in the Variable form"],
    "explanation": ""
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following statements is true about the admin role? (Select 3 Answers)",
    "options": [
      "Non-admin users cannot add users to a group containing the admin role",
      "A user with only the user_admin role can grant the admin role to other users",
      "To grant the admin role to a user, the granting user must also have the admin role",
      "A user with only the admin role cannot grant the security_admin role to other users",
      "A non-admin user with only the security_Admin role can add user to a group that contains the security_Admin role"
    ],
    "correctAnswers": [
      "Non-admin users cannot add users to a group containing the admin role",
      "To grant the admin role to a user, the granting user must also have the admin role",
      "A user with only the admin role cannot grant the security_admin role to other users"
    ],
    "explanation": ""
  },
  {
    "question": "What catalog tool would you use to create a catalog item or record producer?",
    "options": [
      "Catalog formatter",
      "Catalog flow builder",
      "Catalog builder",
      "Catalog designer",
      "Variable designer",
      "Form designer"
    ],
    "correctAnswers": ["Catalog builder"],
    "explanation": ""
  },
  {
    "question": "To quickly return to your instance home page, what item would you click?",
    "options": [
      "Star icon",
      "Shortcuts icon",
      "Navigation header",
      "Gear icon",
      "Instance logo",
      "User menu"
    ],
    "correctAnswers": ["Instance logo"],
    "explanation": ""
  },
  {
    "question": "What function do you use to add buttons, links, and context menu items on forms and lists?",
    "options": ["UI Policies", "UI Settings", "UI Actions", "UI Config"],
    "correctAnswers": ["UI Actions"],
    "explanation": ""
  },
  {
    "question": "Group records are stored in which table?",
    "options": ["Group [sn_user_group]", "Group [sys_user_group]", "Group [s_sys_group]", "Group [u_sys_group]"],
    "correctAnswers": ["Group [sys_user_group]"],
    "explanation": ""
  },
  {
    "question": "Which database provides a logical model of your company infrastructure by identifying, controlling, maintaining and verifying CIs that exist?",
    "options": ["IMDB", "ITSM", "CSDM", "CMDB", "LDAP"],
    "correctAnswers": ["CMDB"],
    "explanation": ""
  },
  {
    "question": "Your customer requires that they be able to monitor which users are performing impersonations in their instance. What would you do to meet that requirement?",
    "options": [
      "Add the role Log Write [sn log write] to the Impersonator Group",
      "Create user update set for impersonation tracking",
      "Activate the glide.sys.log impersonation prop",
      "From User icon, select Elevate Roles",
      "On the Impersonator role record, right click and select Create Log"
    ],
    "correctAnswers": ["Activate the glide.sys.log impersonation prop"],
    "explanation": ""
  },
  {
    "question": "What are benefits of assigning work tasks to a group, rather than to an individual? (Choose four.)",
    "options": [
      "Group members can choose their tasks from My Groups Work",
      "Groups can assign tasks to users based on on-call schedules",
      "Site support members can pick tasks, based on Location",
      "Groups can assign tasks to users based on skills",
      "Group members can avoid tasks, which are nearing SLA breach",
      "Groups can assign tasks to users based on availability"
    ],
    "correctAnswers": [
      "Group members can choose their tasks from My Groups Work",
      "Groups can assign tasks to users based on on-call schedules",
      "Groups can assign tasks to users based on skills",
      "Groups can assign tasks to users based on availability"
    ],
    "explanation": ""
  },
  {
    "question": "What controls the publishing and retiring process for knowledge articles?",
    "options": ["Approval Policies", "Approval Definitions", "Workflow Designer", "Workflows", "State Lifecycle"],
    "correctAnswers": ["Workflows"],
    "explanation": ""
  },
  {
    "question": "Categories in the knowledge base, by default, can be created and edited by which knowledge workers? (Choose two.)",
    "options": [
      "Knowledge Authors",
      "Knowledge Contributors",
      "Knowledge Controller",
      "Knowledge Managers",
      "Knowledge Category Managers",
      "Knowledge Submitters",
      "Knowledge Owners",
      "Knowledge Taxonomy Owner"
    ],
    "correctAnswers": ["Knowledge Contributors", "Knowledge Managers"],
    "explanation": ""
  },
  {
    "question": "What are the components that make up a filter condition? (Choose three.)",
    "options": ["Operator", "Match Criteria", "Value", "Column", "Field"],
    "correctAnswers": ["Operator", "Value", "Field"],
    "explanation": ""
  },
  {
    "question": "What is a key difference between Reporting and Performance Analytics?",
    "options": [
      "Performance Analytics contains snapshots of data taken over time; Reporting shows only the data as it is, at the moment the report is run.",
      "Performance Analytics can show trends; Reports cannot.",
      "Reports can be run on a scheduled basis; Performance Analytics cannot.",
      "Performance Analytics data can be published to Dashboards; Reports cannot.",
      "Performance Analytics shows KPIs; Reporting does not."
    ],
    "correctAnswers": ["Performance Analytics contains snapshots of data taken over time; Reporting shows only the data as it is, at the moment the report is run."],
    "explanation": ""
  },
  {
    "question": "When a user reports that they are not able to see modules on the application navigator, what can you do, to see what modules are visible to them?",
    "options": [
      "Look up their password, so you can login with their account",
      "Initiate a Connect Chat session",
      "Install the Bomgar plug-in",
      "Impersonate the user",
      "Launch a NowChat window"
    ],
    "correctAnswers": ["Impersonate the user"],
    "explanation": ""
  },
  {
    "question": "Which statement correctly describes the differences between a Client Script and a Business Rule?",
    "options": [
      "A Client Script executes before a record is loaded and a Business Rule executes after a record is loaded",
      "A Client Script executes on the server and a Business Rule executes on the client",
      "A Client Script executes on the client and a Business Rule executes on the server",
      "A Client Script executes before a record is loaded and a Business Rule executes after a record is updated"
    ],
    "correctAnswers": ["A Client Script executes on the client and a Business Rule executes on the server"],
    "explanation": ""
  },
  {
    "question": "Which ServiceNow capability allows you to provide knowledge articles, via a conversational messaging interface?",
    "options": ["Agent Assist", "Virtual Agent", "Now Messenger", "Connect Agent"],
    "correctAnswers": ["Agent Assist"],
    "explanation": ""
  },
  {
    "question": "What type of field has a drop down list, from which you can pick from pre-defined options?",
    "options": ["Choice", "Picker", "Drop down", "Option"],
    "correctAnswers": ["Choice"],
    "explanation": ""
  },
  {
    "question": "Which collaboration tool is available from the banner, using the bubble icon?",
    "options": ["Now Messenger", "Agent Chat", "Connect Chat", "Collaborate Now", "Live Feed"],
    "correctAnswers": ["Connect Chat"],
    "explanation": ""
  },
  {
    "question": "User records are stored in which table?",
    "options": ["User [sys_user]", "User [sn_user]", "User [u_sys_user]", "User [s_user]"],
    "correctAnswers": ["User [sys_user]"],
    "explanation": ""
  },
  {
    "question": "Which ServiceNow capability provides assistance to help users obtain information, make decisions, and perform common work tasks via a messaging interface?",
    "options": ["Agent Workspace", "Chat bot", "Virtual Agent", "Knowledge Chat", "Now Support"],
    "correctAnswers": ["Virtual Agent"],
    "explanation": ""
  },
  {
    "question": "While showing a customer their incident form, they ask to change the Priority values to display their internal terminology P1, P2, P3, P4. They want it to be consistent across all Tasks. How would you do that? Right click on Priority and select what?",
    "options": ["Configure Lists", "Show Options", "Configure Task", "Show Choices", "Show Choice List", "Configure Options"],
    "correctAnswers": ["Show Choice List"],
    "explanation": ""
  },
  {
    "question": "When a flow runs an action, it generates a runtime value, which stays the same for the duration of the flow. What is the name of this runtime value?",
    "options": ["Trigger runtime value", "Sequence runtime value", "Starting runtime value", "Data pill runtime value", "Input runtime value"],
    "correctAnswers": ["Data pill runtime value"],
    "explanation": ""
  },
  {
    "question": "What ServiceNow feature allows you to include data from a secondary related table on a report?",
    "options": ["SQL", "Dot Walking", "Outer Join", "Joins"],
    "correctAnswers": ["Dot Walking"],
    "explanation": ""
  },
  {
    "question": "Which collaboration tool opens a sidebar and allows you to create new conversations with other ServiceNow users?",
    "options": ["Skype Now", "Collaborate Now", "Agent Messenger", "Agent Chat", "Connect Chat"],
    "correctAnswers": ["Agent Chat"],
    "explanation": ""
  },
  {
    "question": "When you need to orchestrate business processes across services with little technical user knowledge, which utility would you use?",
    "options": ["Flow Manager", "Flow Designer", "Flow Editor", "Workflow Editor", "Workflow Designer"],
    "correctAnswers": ["Flow Designer"],
    "explanation": ""
  },
  {
    "question": "What module would you use if you wanted to view a list of all of the fields on the Incident table? (Choose two.)",
    "options": ["Tables & Columns", "Dictionary", "Data Class Manager", "Dictionary Dashboard", "Database View", "Schema"],
    "correctAnswers": ["Tables & Columns", "Dictionary"],
    "explanation": ""
  },
  {
    "question": "What feature do you use to specify which users are able to access a Service Catalog Item?",
    "options": ["Can Read Role", "Catalog User Role", "Can Order Tab", "User Criteria"],
    "correctAnswers": ["User Criteria"],
    "explanation": ""
  },
  {
    "question": "What are advantages of using Flow Designer? (Choose three.)",
    "options": [
      "Supports advanced developers",
      "Enables complicated scripting",
      "Reduces technical debt",
      "Less manual scripting",
      "Smooth integration with 3rd party systems"
    ],
    "correctAnswers": ["Reduces technical debt", "Less manual scripting", "Smooth integration with 3rd party systems"],
    "explanation": ""
  },
  {
    "question": "Which type of policy would you use to meet this requirement: 'Incident numbers should be read only on all lists and forms for all users. Short Description field should be mandatory on all records, across all applications, on Insert.'?",
    "options": ["Data Quality Policy", "Dictionary Design Policy", "UI Data Policy", "UI Policy", "Field Criteria Policy", "Data Policy"],
    "correctAnswers": ["Data Policy"],
    "explanation": ""
  },
  {
    "question": "What type of field is Boolean and appears as a check box?",
    "options": ["Yes/No", "True/False", "On/Off", "Binary", "0/1"],
    "correctAnswers": ["True/False"],
    "explanation": ""
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the most common role that has access to almost all platform features, functions, and data?",
    "options": [
      "Security Admin [security admin]",
      "Sys Admin [sys admin]",
      "Admin [sn admin]",
      "System Administrator [admin]",
      "Base Admin [base admin]"
    ],
    "correctAnswers": ["System Administrator [admin]"],
    "explanation": ""
  },
  {
    "question": "When impersonating a user for testing purposes, what is the best way to return the instance, logged in with your user account?",
    "options": ["Turn your computer off and on again", "Clear browser cache", "End Impersonation", "Log out and back in"],
    "correctAnswers": ["End Impersonation"],
    "explanation": ""
  },
  {
    "question": "When importing data, what happens to imported rows if no coalesce field is specified?",
    "options": [
      "All rows are rejected from the import, as coalesce field is required.",
      "All rows are treated as new records. No existing records are updated.",
      "Duplicate rows are rejected from the import.",
      "All rows are treated as new records, but errors will be flagged in the import log."
    ],
    "correctAnswers": ["All rows are treated as new records. No existing records are updated."],
    "explanation": ""
  },
  {
    "question": "Which module is used as the first step for importing data?",
    "options": ["Coalesce Data", "Transform Data", "Import Data", "Load Data"],
    "correctAnswers": ["Load Data"],
    "explanation": ""
  },
  {
    "question": "A Role is defined as what?",
    "options": [
      "A collection of permissions",
      "A set of user access policies",
      "A Persona in a workflow",
      "A set of access control rules"
    ],
    "correctAnswers": ["A collection of permissions"],
    "explanation": ""
  },
  {
    "question": "You are asked to create an option in the Service Catalog which will allow a user to click Get Help and describe the issue they are having. These forms should create incident records, which are automatically routed to the Service Desk. Which method would you use?",
    "options": [
      "Create Record Producer",
      "Create Catalog Item",
      "Create Order Guide",
      "Create Content Item"
    ],
    "correctAnswers": ["Create Record Producer"],
    "explanation": ""
  },
  {
    "question": "Which tool graphically displays an infrastructure view for a configuration item (CI) and its relationship with other CIs?",
    "options": ["Schema Map", "Dependency View", "Dependency Map", "Database View"],
    "correctAnswers": ["Dependency View"],
    "explanation": ""
  },
  {
    "question": "Which module is used to access the knowledge bases which are available to you?",
    "options": [
      "Knowledge > Home",
      "Self Service > Knowledge",
      "Knowledge > All",
      "Knowledge > Knowledge Bases",
      "Knowledge > Overview"
    ],
    "correctAnswers": ["Self Service > Knowledge"],
    "explanation": ""
  },
  {
    "question": "Which component of a table contains a piece of data for one record?",
    "options": ["Factor", "Field", "Datapoint", "Element", "Item"],
    "correctAnswers": ["Field"],
    "explanation": ""
  },
  {
    "question": "What type of query allows you to filter list data using normal words, instead of the condition builder?",
    "options": [
      "Natural Language Query",
      "Alexa Query",
      "Machine Learning Query",
      "Predictive Intelligence Query",
      "Auto-suggest Query"
    ],
    "correctAnswers": ["Natural Language Query"],
    "explanation": ""
  },
  {
    "question": "Which field (or fields) is used as a unique key during imports?",
    "options": ["Match Fields", "Coalesce Fields", "Key Fields", "Sys IDs"],
    "correctAnswers": ["Coalesce Fields"],
    "explanation": ""
  },
  {
    "question": "On the Reports page, what sections allow you to see which reports are visible to different audiences? (Choose four.)",
    "options": ["Group", "Department", "My reports", "Team", "Dashboards", "Global", "Admin", "Analytics", "All", "Company"],
    "correctAnswers": ["Group", "My reports", "Global", "All"],
    "explanation": ""
  },
  {
    "question": "What would you do, on a list, if you wanted to show the records in groups, based on the column category? (Choose two.)",
    "options": [
      "On list Context Menu, select Group By > Category",
      "On the Filter Menu, select Group By > Category",
      "Click Group On icon, select Category",
      "On Navigator Filter, type tablename.group.category and press enter",
      "On the Category column title, click Context menu > Group By Category"
    ],
    "correctAnswers": [
      "On list Context Menu, select Group By > Category",
      "On the Category column title, click Context menu > Group By Category"
    ],
    "explanation": ""
  },
  {
    "question": "Which module would you use to customize your instance’s banner image, text and colors?",
    "options": [
      "System UI > UI Pages > Branding",
      "Service Portal > Portals > Branding",
      "System Properties > Basic Configuration UI16",
      "System Properties > Branding",
      "Homepage Admin > Pages > Branding"
    ],
    "correctAnswers": ["System Properties > Basic Configuration UI16"],
    "explanation": ""
  },
  {
    "question": "What are examples of Core tables in the ServiceNow platform?",
    "options": ["Configuration, Connect, Chat", "Team, Party, Awards", "User, Task, Incident", "Work, Caller, Timecard"],
    "correctAnswers": ["User, Task, Incident"],
    "explanation": ""
  },
  {
    "question": "What attributes can you manage, using System Properties > Basic Configuration UI16? (Choose five.)",
    "options": [
      "Browser tab title",
      "Module text color",
      "Preferred browser",
      "Base theme",
      "Font style",
      "Animation style",
      "Header background color",
      "Banner Image"
    ],
    "correctAnswers": ["Browser tab title", "Module text color", "Base theme", "Header background color", "Banner Image"],
    "explanation": ""
  },
  {
    "question": "On the knowledge base record, which tab would you use to define which users are not able to write articles to the knowledge base?",
    "options": ["Can Contribute", "Cannot Author", "Cannot Contribute", "Cannot Write", "Read Only"],
    "correctAnswers": ["Cannot Contribute"],
    "explanation": ""
  },
  {
    "question": "A manager wants to view a snapshot of month-end Sales performance data, as compared to Sales targets. In addition, the manager wants to be able to see those monthly numbers trended over time, and forecasted into the future. What capability do you suggest for this manager?",
    "options": [
      "Scheduled Reports, a custom snapshot table, and a Trend report",
      "Scheduled Reports and Excel",
      "Scheduled Reports, a custom snapshot table, and a Projection report",
      "Performance Analytics",
      "Key Performance Indicators"
    ],
    "correctAnswers": ["Performance Analytics"],
    "explanation": ""
  },
  {
    "question": "On a filter condition, which component is always a choice list?",
    "options": ["Operator", "Filter Criteria", "Operation", "Match Criteria"],
    "correctAnswers": ["Operator"],
    "explanation": ""
  },
  {
    "question": "A user is complaining that they are seeing a blank page, when they click Create New, from your custom Inventory application. You have confirmed that they can see the Inventory application and the Create New module on the application navigator. What could be the cause of this issue?",
    "options": [
      "Create New module has a broken link",
      "Known intermittent issue with UIM5",
      "User should be using Chrome instead of Explorer for their browser",
      "User has read role, but not the write role on the Inventory table",
      "User session has timed out"
    ],
    "correctAnswers": ["User has read role, but not the write role on the Inventory table"],
    "explanation": ""
  },
  {
    "question": "What ServiceNow feature can be triggered by events, and is used to inform users about activities or updates in ServiceNow?",
    "options": ["Notifications", "Alerts", "Texts", "Events", "Emails"],
    "correctAnswers": ["Notifications"],
    "explanation": ""
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the name of the table relationship, where two or more tables are related in a bi-directional relationship, so that the related records are visible from both tables in a related list?",
    "options": ["Database View", "Many to Many", "One to Many", "Extended"],
    "correctAnswers": ["Many to Many"],
    "explanation": ""
  },
  {
    "question": "Which feature allows you to automate business logic for a particular application or process such as approvals, tasks notifications, and record operations?",
    "options": ["Flows", "Action Sequences", "Action Sets", "Task Flows", "Flow Diagrams"],
    "correctAnswers": ["Flows"],
    "explanation": ""
  },
  {
    "question": "From a form, what would you click to add additional fields to the form? (Choose two.)",
    "options": [
      "Context Menu > Form > Layout",
      "Context Menu > Configure > Form Layout",
      "Context Menu > Configure > Form Design",
      "Right click on header > Add > Field",
      "Context Menu > Form > Designer",
      "Right click on header > Configure > UX Dashboard"
    ],
    "correctAnswers": ["Context Menu > Configure > Form Layout", "Context Menu > Configure > Form Design"],
    "explanation": ""
  },
  {
    "question": "Which tool is used to define relationships between fields in an import set table and a target table?",
    "options": ["Transform Schema", "Schema Map", "Dictionary Map", "Transform Map", "Field Transformer", "Import Designer"],
    "correctAnswers": ["Transform Map"],
    "explanation": ""
  },
  {
    "question": "Tables may have a One to Many relationship. From the Service Catalog, what are examples of tables having a one to many relationship? (Choose three.)",
    "options": [
      "One Approval can have many Requests",
      "One Request can have many Requested Items",
      "One Requested Item can have many Approvals",
      "One Requested Item can have many Catalog Tasks",
      "One Cart can have many Requests"
    ],
    "correctAnswers": [
      "One Request can have many Requested Items",
      "One Requested Item can have many Approvals",
      "One Requested Item can have many Catalog Tasks"
    ],
    "explanation": ""
  },
  {
    "question": "What component causes a flow to run after a record has been created or updated?",
    "options": ["Date-based trigger", "On-change trigger", "Record-based trigger", "Application-based trigger", "Updated-date trigger"],
    "correctAnswers": ["Record-based trigger"],
    "explanation": ""
  },
  {
    "question": "On a Form header, what is the three bar icon called?",
    "options": ["Pancake icon", "Additional Actions or Context Menu", "Hamburger icon", "Cake icon"],
    "correctAnswers": ["Additional Actions or Context Menu"],
    "explanation": ""
  },
  {
    "question": "Which role can manage multiple knowledge bases?",
    "options": ["knowledge-base_admin", "kb_admin", "sn_kb_admin", "knowledge_admin"],
    "correctAnswers": ["knowledge_admin"],
    "explanation": ""
  },
  {
    "question": "What resource can you use to view details of the tables and configuration items (CIs) associated with a particular use case?",
    "options": ["Scenario Dashboard", "CI Use Case Modeler", "CMDB Use Case Modeler", "Common Service Data Model (CSDM) product view"],
    "correctAnswers": ["Common Service Data Model (CSDM) product view"],
    "explanation": ""
  },
  {
    "question": "Which features allow you to update multiple records at one time? (Choose two.)",
    "options": ["List Editor", "Field Update Action", "Bulk Record Update", "Data Remediation Dashboard", "Update Selected Action"],
    "correctAnswers": ["List Editor", "Update Selected Action"],
    "explanation": ""
  },
  {
    "question": "What type of user (persona) has clearly defined paths and workflows in the platform and have one or more roles (ie itil and approver user)?",
    "options": ["Workflow User", "Request Fulfiller", "ITSM User", "Approving Manager", "Service Desk User", "Process User"],
    "correctAnswers": ["Process User"],
    "explanation": ""
  },
  {
    "question": "Your customer would like to create a new template to notify users who are affected by network outages at their site. Which module would you use to create a new notification?",
    "options": [
      "System Notification > Email > Notifications",
      "Administration > Notification Overview",
      "System Properties > Email > Settings",
      "User Preferences > Email > Notifications",
      "Click Gear > Notifications > New"
    ],
    "correctAnswers": ["System Notification > Email > Notifications"],
    "explanation": ""
  },
  {
    "question": "The wait time for end users is based on the round-trip between the client and the server. What activities are included in the round-trips?",
    "options": ["Request + Response", "Save + Update", "Write + Read", "Submit + Query", "Insert + Verify"],
    "correctAnswers": ["Request + Response"],
    "explanation": ""
  },
  {
    "question": "On a Business Rule, the When setting determines at what point the rule executes. What are the options for specifying that timing?",
    "options": [
      "Before, After, Async, Display",
      "Prior to, Synchronous, on Update",
      "Insert, Update, Delete, Query",
      "Before, Synchronous, Scheduled Job, View"
    ],
    "correctAnswers": ["Before, After, Async, Display"],
    "explanation": ""
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the result of the order in which access controls are evaluated?",
    "options": [
      "Ensures user has access to the fields in a table, before considering their access to the table",
      "Ensures user can get to work as quickly as possible",
      "Ensures user has access to the application, before evaluating access to a module within the application",
      "Ensures user has access to a table, before evaluating access to a field in the table"
    ],
    "correctAnswers": ["Ensures user has access to a table, before evaluating access to a field in the table"],
    "explanation": ""
  },
  {
    "question": "What are different types of Data Sources, which may be imported into ServiceNow? (Choose four.)",
    "options": ["Local Sources (i.e. XML, CSV, Excel)", "Implementation Spoke", "DataHub", "JDBC Connection", "Network Server", "LDAP Connection"],
    "correctAnswers": ["Local Sources (i.e. XML, CSV, Excel)", "JDBC Connection", "Network Server", "LDAP Connection"],
    "explanation": ""
  },
  {
    "question": "When designing a flow, how do you reference data from a record, in that flow?",
    "options": [
      "Drag the table icon onto the flow definition",
      "Use the condition builder to specify the desired values",
      "Specify the source table on the data pill related list",
      "Drag the data pill onto the flow definition",
      "Add the table reference using the slush bucket"
    ],
    "correctAnswers": ["Drag the data pill onto the flow definition"],
    "explanation": ""
  }
]
